<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Love at First Sight</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">A Brief Overview</string>
    <string name="article_text">
       Love at first sight means that you feel an instant connection to another person, according to Dubrow. “Some people describe this as fireworks, others describe it as moments where
        \n nothing else matters around you when you see and talk to each other for the first time. It is the feeling you get when you dont want a moment to end because you feel a connection
        \n with another person that you have not felt before. To Paredes, love at first sight is a strong, intense electricity type of feeling that is a product of chemistry between two people.
        \n She explains, It can be very euphoric and exhilarating. I have been told by patients that it was a similar feeling to being drunk you are completely engulfed in the feeling.
        \n For others who have felt it and hoped it would last forever—they have described it as an immediate sense of a person” even if you only see them from across the room at a party, or get introduced
        \n when a new person joins the company you work for, or a friend brings someone new along for an evening out. It is an immediate reaction, usually first about the way a person looks, how they are dressed,
        \n their physical motions, their voice, and how they look at you, adds O Neill. There is a feeling in ones gut that there is something special about this person that you are instantly attracted to, and
        \n you sense quickly that they feel the same way. It can be very euphoric and exhilarating. I have been told by patients that it was a similar feeling to being drunk you are completely engulfed in the feeling.
        \n For others who have felt it and hoped it would last forever—they have described it as an immediate sense of a person” even if you only see them from across the room at a party, or get introduced
        \n when a new person joins the company you work for.
</string>
</resources>